Steve Earle

[6043 Welsford Street, Apt 2.] [Halifax, Nova Scotia, B3K 1G3] [902-219-2072] [searle@programmer.net]

About Me

I am a first-year NSCC student currently completing a diploma in the IT Programming focus at NSCC. In addition to my academic background, I have experience in online marketing, as well as networking and public presentation, from many years spent as an internationally touring musician and local promoter.

Experience

Programming

NSCC September 2017 – Present Halifax, Nova Scotia

Currently completing my studies.

My skills include:

- Writing code in Python 3
- Designing applications using PyQt5
- Data management using SQL
- Windows Administration using Powershell

Web Development

NSCC September 2017 Halifax, Nova Scotia

Currently completing my studies.

My skills include:

- Creating web pages using HTML5
- Styling web pages using CSS3

Event Organizer

Self Employed: July 2013 – Present Halifax, Nova Scotia

Experience:

- Promotion through social media, online advertising, and physical press coverage.
- Graphic Design for event posters using Photoshop.
- Booking concerts for various bands in, or touring through Halifax, N.S.
- Working with and creating relationships with a diverse range of venues.
- Creating and maintaining safe, welcoming, and inclusive spaces.
- Consulting with other organizers for event coordination.

Steve Earle

[6043 Welsford Street, Apt. 2] [Halifax, Nova Scotia, B3K 1G3] [902-219-2072] [searle@programmer.net]

Academic Education

Nova Scotia Community College Dates of Attendance: September 2017 – Present

Currently completing a diploma in IT Programming

Prince Andrew High School, Dartmouth, Nova Scotia Dates of Attendance: September 2008 – February 2012

Completed grade 12

References

Ms. Adair Townsend Retired Teacher

Home Phone: 902-462-4563Cell Phone: 902-266-4232

Mr. Ray MacNeil

Corporate Strategist for Nova Scotia Communities, Culture, and Heritage

Home Phone: 902-430-5836